# Ravid Katz

Industrial
Engineering and
Management
Student

#### Contact



052-6589200



ravid2108@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ravidkatz

### **Education**

2021-present

# 3rd-Year student Industrial Engineering and Management B.SC

at the Ruppin Academic Center

• 2020-2021

Graduate of a designated engineering preparatory program.

High School

Majored in Electrics and electronics.

## **Expertise**

- C++, C#
- Database Skilled in SQL server, database planning, Entity-Relationship
   Diagram (ERD), Microsoft ACCESS.
- HTML
- Microsoft Office
- Advanced Excel

## Language

- English
- Hebrw

#### **About Me**

Excellent interpersonal skills, teamwork experience, and understanding of others' needs.

Effective in handling complex challenges.

Highly motivated for success and advancement.

Strong work ethic and ability to learn quickly under pressure.

Experienced in team management.

### Experience

## $\mathsf{P}$ Project Manager in the worlds of environmental quality

2023- today

#### Eldad Sharoni environmental engineering LTD

- Student job
- Providing consulting services and assistance on the subject in all projects.
- Information analysis and statistical analyzes in a huge database of data and pollutant monitoring.
- Providing advice/planning and data collection with governmental and local authorities.
- Working with external suppliers and preparing materials for tenders.
- Monitoring processes and preparing project status.

#### O Bar Manager

2018-2020

#### Beach Club.Tel Aviv

- I have established and managed the Bar, including the processes of recruitment, selection, and screening of employees through comprehensive and precise job interviews, which also involve overlapping and training procedures.
- I have led and managed the Bar and Restaurant team effectively under constant pressure from end to end. I have been responsible for inventory management, warehouse management, ordering goods from suppliers, and handling negotiations and transactions with them.
- I have had full and comprehensive responsibility for organizing work schedules, preparing weekly schedules, and distributing salaries to the team.

## Military Service

## Aircraft technician first class - Hercules aircraft, in squadron 131 2015-2018

- Responsible for advanced aviation software and aircraft preparation for flight, removal, and receipt.
- Checked the usability of aircraft on a daily basis and participated in operational activities.
- Holder of a certificate of appreciation from the squadron commander.
- Certifications: Technician Level A.
- Certificate of profession: Mechanical Maintenance.

#### Volunteer

- FIDF IMPACT in the HaShomer HaChadash
- Avichail Gemach

## Citizenship

- Israeli
- Portuguese